(Sheldon:)This on a night
that I had originally designated...
...for solving space-time geometry
in higher-spin gravity...
(Sheldon:)...and building my Lego Death Star.
(Sheldon:)And why?
(Sheldon:)Your gal pals, Penny and Bernadette...
(Sheldon:)...went out shopping for
some wedding nonsense without Amy...
(Sheldon:)...an action they took with no thought
as to how it would affect me...
(Sheldon:)...the future of string theory
or my Lego fun time.
(Howard:)What do you want us to do about it?
You weren't listening
to my topic sentence.
(Sheldon:)Get your women in line.
(Sheldon:)Make them apologize to Amy
and set things right.
(Sheldon:)I am a man of science,
not someone's snuggle bunny.
(Leonard:)Why do I have to talk to Penny?
She's not my girIfriend.
You invited her to Iunch
four years ago.
(Sheldon:)Everything about her is on you.
You make it so.
- Moo Shu is Penny.
- Thank you.
(Penny:)- Where's Sheldon?
- Oh, he was up late last night...
(Leonard:)...so I gave him an early dinner
and put him to bed.
(Bernadette:)That's so sweet.
(Leonard:)Yeah, but now he's gonna be up
at dawn and wanna play.